getmeaticket.co.uk 2016-04-25

# Privacy Policy | Free Competitions Online | Get Me A Ticket

**About this privacy policy**

This policy sets out how we will use and share the information that you give us or allow us to obtain from third parties.

Get Me A Ticket is a trading name of Callcredit Lead Generation Limited which is registered in England with company number 5373447 and has its registered office at One Park Lane, Leeds, West Yorkshire LS3 1EP. Callcredit Lead Generation Limited is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office under the Data Protection Act 1998; its registration number is Z9141445. When we refer to “we”, “us”, or “Get Me A Ticket” we are referring to this company.

You can get in touch with us in any of the following ways:

**By email:** [support@getmeaticket.co.uk](mailto:support@getmeaticket.co.uk)

**Through this website:** <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/contact>

**By post:** Consumer Queries, Get Me A Ticket, 7-9 North Parade Building, Bath, BA1 1NS

**Who this privacy policy applies to**

This policy applies to individuals who have registered with Get Me A Ticket and websites to which Get Me A Ticket provides competition services. Parts of this privacy policy also apply to all users of the website.

**What this policy applies to**

This policy applies to the information about yourself that you choose to provide us with or that you allow us to collect. This includes:

  * information you provide during the registration process, such as your name, your age and your contact details,
  * information you provide when you enter prize draws, quizzes, competitions or answer surveys, such as information about your lifestyle including your hobbies, interests and online habits,
  * information you provide when you answer surveys,
  * information which we may obtain about you from third parties (for example, because you have given third parties permission to share that information with us),
  * information we collect about how you use the website.

**Our obligations**

We are a data controller in relation to the information that you provide us with. As a result, we are legally responsible for how that information is handled.

We will comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 in the way we use and share your personal data. Among other things, this means that we will only use your personal data:

  * fairly and lawfully,
  * as set out in the legislation and this policy,
  * to the extent necessary for these purposes.

We may process your personal data ourselves or through data processors who will process data on our behalf. If we use data processors we will remain responsible for ensuring that they comply with this policy and data protection law.

We will take every reasonable precaution to safeguard the personal information that you supply.

If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries about our privacy policy, website or service, please contact us using the details given above.

**Marketing and relationship management**

We may use your information to provide you with information about goods and services which we think may be of interest to you and for relationship management.

We may also from time to time supply your information to third parties for marketing or relationship management purposes. The main purposes to which your data are put are to allow third parties to provide you with information about goods and services which they think may be of interest to you and/or to maintain any existing relationship they may have with you. Such information may be provided by marketing communications or advertising which is tailored to your interests. Your data may also be used in the way described below. Be assured that any such parties will only be allowed to use your data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable law relating to privacy.

Those third parties who would wish to send you marketing communications or to advertise to you will fall into the following categories:

Sector | Description and examples  
---|---  
Retail | 

  * Online retail
  * General stores
  * Automotive (including dealerships and accessories)
  * Property
  * Home furnishings
  * Home improvement
  * Fashion and clothing
  * Telecoms and utilities
  * GoGroopie
  * Reebok

Finance | 

  * Pensions
  * Loans, credit cards and mortgages
  * Investments & savings
  * Insurance Home
  * Car
  * Travel
  * Pet
  * Personal
  * Other insurances

Travel | 

  * Holidays
  * Hotel
  * Airlines
  * Travel booking
  * Cheapflights
  * Dealchecker

Lifestyle | 

  * Health & Well-being
  * Fitness
  * Charities
  * Media & publishing companies
  * Leisure
  * Gaming
  * Legal Services
  * Educational institutions
  * Oxygem
  * Lightspeed

**Scope of Consent**

By submitting your personal data on this site, whether in those fields marked mandatory or otherwise, you are affirming your consent for such information to be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You will be able to withdraw that consent at any time by the methods described below.

If you **do** tick any of the boxes in the fair processing notice inviting you to give your consent, those third parties **may** contact you by the channels which you have ticked. So, for example, if you tick the post and e-mail boxes, that means that third parties falling in the categories listed above can contact you via post and e-mail but not by the other channels.

If you opt in to telephone calls you are consenting to receiving live calls and recorded calls.

By continuing to use this website you have consented to information being collected from your device by cookies or other similar technologies, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including the display of targeted advertising based on the information provided.

**Opting out at a later date**

Once you have given your consent, you can however still control whether or not you continue to receive communications or see such advertisements from such third parties. The method of control depends on the channel of communication or advertising:

**Post**

You can also withdraw your consent for **postal marketing** from anyone by adding your details to the **Mail Preference Service**. For more details please go to [www.mpsonline.org.uk](http://www.mpsonline.org.uk/).

**E-mail or SMS (text message)**

You can unsubscribe from receiving **e-mail or SMS marketing communications** from any individual third party by using the instructions in any email communication such third party sends you (usually an ' **unsubscribe** ' or ' **STOP** ' link).

**Telephone calls**

To withdraw your consent for **live or automated calls** from anyone you can add your name to the **Telephone Preference Service** which is maintained at this website address: [www.tpsonline.org.uk](http://www.tpsonline.org.uk/).

You can also opt out at any time from communications via any of the methods described above through <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/unsubscribe> or by contacting us at <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/contact>. Please note that such opt-out will only apply to communications from those third parties with whom we have a business relationship. If you opt out this way, you may still receive communications from third parties with whom we have no relationship.

**Social media and online**

You can configure your advertising preferences on social media such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram or Pinterest by accessing your settings or preference options on the relevant platform.

If you no longer want to receive personalized advertising on any website you visit, you can usually opt out directly through the privacy policy of the particular website you are accessing. Please note that this will not block ads that are displayed on the websites you visit, it will simply stop you receiving advertising that has been tailored to your interests. This opt-out relies on a cookie, so if you wipe all your cookies then that website will no longer know that you have opted out. The same applies if you use a different internet browser, or use a new computer to access the internet. You can also opt out of such advertising by visiting the IAB opt-out platform at [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). Please note that this and other platforms allow you to opt out of interest-based advertising delivered by registered members.

**Combining data**

The information you give us may be combined with other information about you that is obtained from other sources. The combination is usually undertaken with a view to enhancing an existing database with more information. For example:

  * If you are already a customer of a third party, that third party might wish to add an e-mail address you give us to the customer records that it holds about you, and use that email address to maintain their relationship with you and/or to offer you goods and services that are similar to those you have previously purchased.
  * The data you provide here may be combined with data you have provided elsewhere to verify your identity or validate the information you have provided (for example in the context of a third party’s anti-fraud measures.
  * If you have given any third parties permission to share your information, or if you sign in through a social medium, those third parties may be able to find and use information about you so that, in order to speed up the registration process or offer you tailored advertising, you don't have to provide the information directly to us. The information we obtain will be used in accordance with the other parts of this privacy policy.

The consent you provided for any information you have previously shared with us or any third parties will be renewed at the time you give your consent for any new information sharing unless you indicate otherwise by contacting us, by contacting us at <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/contact>.

**Analysis and derivative data products**

Sometimes your data will be used for analysis purposes or to build data products. In these instances, the information is aggregated and wherever possible anonymised in line with the Information

**Legitimate Interests**

**Under the Data Protection Act, we are also permitted to share some information with third parties who use such data for non-marketing purposes (including credit and risk assessment and management, identification and fraud prevention, debt collection and returning assets to you). This would include the data you provide to us today, at any time in the past and in the future.**

**Prize draws**

If you wish to enter a prize draw you may be required to complete a survey from one of our partners. These surveys may have their own privacy policies and consent statements. We recommend that you read and understand this information before agreeing to it.

**Part registration**

If you begin to register on Get Me A Ticket but do not complete the registration, we may temporarily collect and store the information you have provided so that we may contact you. For example, we may send you operational emails to enquire about why the registration was not completed. This information will not be used for any other purpose, will not be stored for longer than necessary and will not be shared with third parties. Our aim is simply to provide you with the highest level of service that we can.

If you have any queries or concerns about the data usage please contact us using the form provided on this page: <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/contact>.

**Retention and destruction of personal information**

We will take reasonable steps to ensure the accuracy of the information we hold about you. We will not use your personal information unless it is (to the best of our knowledge) accurate and up to date.

We will not keep your personal information for longer than necessary. Once it has been decided that the information is no longer needed, it will be deleted promptly.

**Your choices in relation to personal information**

You have the right to:

  * obtain access to your personal information,
  * receive information about us and the purposes for which we process your personal data,
  * prevent processing which may cause you damage or distress,
  * object to direct marketing,
  * object to purely automated decision-making in certain cases,
  * ask us to correct any errors or delete the information we hold,
  * opt out of further contact.

If you would like to amend or delete your details or contact us in relation to the use of your personal information, please contact using this page: <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/contact>. To change your communication preferences please use the form provided here: <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/unsubscribe>.

**Additional disclosure of your information**

If our business (or a significant part of it) offered for sale, your personal information may be given to the prospective buyer, who will be able to use it to help them evaluate the proposed sale. If the sale is completed, the buyer will be able to continue using your information in accordance with this privacy policy.

We will also disclose your personal data if we are under a legal obligation to do so.

**Security**

Unfortunately, the transmission of data over the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its security. Once we have received your data we will use strict security measures to try to protect it against loss, misuse, or unauthorised alterations.

We will also require any third parties with whom we share your information to keep the information secure.

**IP address and cookies**

We may collect information about your computer including your IP address, operating system and browser type for system administration and to report aggregate information to our client sponsors and advertisers.

For the same reason we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using cookies. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service to you. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the cookies. To understand more about cookie based advertising, please visit [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note that restricting cookies may affect your ability to access certain parts of the site.

By continuing to use this website you agree to the cookies listed below being placed on your computer.

Name | Purpose More Information  
---|---  
  
  * _utma
  * _utmb
  * _utmc
  * _utmz

| These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they have visited. <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html>  
  
**Changes**

We may change the terms of this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted on this page.

**Contacting us, exercising your information rights and Complaints**

If you any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, wish to exercise your information rights in connection with the personal data you have shared with us or wish to complain, please contact:

**By email:** [support@getmeaticket.co.uk](mailto:support@getmeaticket.co.uk)

**Through this website:** <http://www.getmeaticket.co.uk/contact>

**By post:** 7-9 North Parade Building, Bath, BA1 1NS
